okay so this is an unpopular opinion but what else is new um i just think logan was the best
option for worry and i i don't even understand why we're talking about dean or jess like
there was a difference between which boyfriend made the most sense and obviously logan was the
mature boyfriend like jess was like you know when you're in high school and you're like oh my god
he's so mysterious and then like dean i mean dean was like when you're in high school and you're just
like wow like this is a really nice guy but like logan made the most sense now was logan also a part
of like the eyes wide shut at their school yes and so does that mean that rory might actually be a part
of like the illuminati yes if you were wondering how this ties into what's going on right now
but i just i can't i'm not gonna have that argument with you guys anymore it's logan all the way
how black am i gonna have to get there are two issues of our time really that i think
amount to a litmus test for morality as far as i'm concerned one is what you're prepared to do on
behalf of the palestinian people and the other is what are you prepared to do on behalf of gay and
lesbian people